BREAKING THE CYCLE DOESN'T REQUIRE
WOMEN TO WALK ON EGGSHELLS
OR TOLERATE BAD BEHAVIOR IT
SIMPLY REQUIRES UNDERSTANDING THE THREE
PSYCHOLOGICAL TRIGGERS THAT MAKE A
MAN FEEL FIERCELY DEVOTED SIGNAL
ONE PUBLIC LOYALTY A MAN
WILL FORGIVE ALMOST ANY PRIVATE
DISAGREEMENT BUT CRITICIZE HIM MOCK
HIM OR ROLL YOUR EYES
IN FRONT OF FRIENDS OR
FAMILY AND YOU INFLICT A
WOUND THAT TAKES MONTHS TO
HEAL WHEN YOU BACK HIM
UP IN PUBLIC HE FEELS
INVINCIBLE SIGNAL TWO SEEKING HIS
COUNSEL NOTHING MAKES A MAN
FEEL RESPECTED FASTER THAN ASKING
WHAT DO YOU THINK WE
SHOULD DO ABOUT THIS IT
SIGNALS THAT HIS MIND AND
JUDGMENT ARE VALUABLE TO YOU
SIGNAL THREE ACKNOWLEDGING EFFORT BEFORE
CORRECTION IF HE FIXED SOMETHING
OR WORKED LATE SAY THANK
YOU FOR TAKING CARE OF
THAT BEFORE POINTING OUT WHAT'S
MISSING